export const QuizData = [
    {
        question: "What is ReactJS?",
        options: ["Server-side framework", "user interface framework", "Both A and B", "None of the above"],
      answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Which company developed ReactJS",
        options: ["Apple", "Facebook", "Google", "Twitter"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is used in React.js to increase performance?",
        options: ["Virtual DOM", "Original DOM", "Both A and B", "None of the above"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What is Babel?",
        options: ["Javascript compiler", "Javascript interpreter", "Javascript transpiler", "None of the above"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following port is the default where webpack-dev-server runs?",
        options: ["3000", "3306", "8080", "3030"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "How many elements can a valid react component return?",
        options: ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following method is used to access the state of a component from inside of a member function?",
        options: ["this.prototype.stateValue", "this.getValue()", "this.values", "this.state"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "In MVC, what does React.js act as?",
        options: ["model", "controller", "view", "middleware"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Identify the one which is used to pass data to components from outside",
        options: ["redner with arguements", "setState", "propTypes", "props"],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "When is useReducer used over useState in React component?",
        options: ["When we want to replace redux", "when we want to break our production app", "when we want to improve performance", "none of the above"],
        answer: 1
    },
];